I knew I couldn't do this kind of place.
I haven't been in a bathroom in forever.
Hey, guys.
How do you light a fire in a tree?
I don't know.
Help me, please.
Today...
I've come to play bamboo shoots.
New hat.
New clothes.
I came in the rain.
It was so hard to get here.
It was kind of a mess.
We took a lot of weird roads.
We went through a lot of mountains.
I'm tired of driving.
I'm very tired.
But I'm going to do it
I'm going to set it up.
We're all set up.
I did, but it was so hard!
It's so sunny!
I'm going to try and get a fire going right now.
I want you to listen to me.
They didn't have any credit paper.
They only sold government paper.
I'm not sure if I can make a fire with government paper.
I'm not sure.
I'll do my best! Watch me and I'll do my best!
Thank you for watching!
I knew I couldn't do it like this.
That's nice.
I'll have to stir it up a bit.
Day 3
On the third day, we crossed Haneda Airport from Mt,
Haneda Airport station, about an hour and a half away.
From Haneda Airport station,
Haneda Airport station is 3.5 hours away from Haneda Airport station.
From Haneda Airport Sta,
It takes about 1.5 hours from Haneda Airport station.
Hajime Shacho Ending
El Dong Ling
Thank you for your hard work.
Amazing.
I can't help it
And I don't even have a writer today.
I'm doing great.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, well, let's see if I can start a fire.
You might like it.
I'll see you at about 2:30.
Thank you for watching.
Guys, how do you light a fire on a maple tree?
How do you light it?
I don't know.
Help me, somebody.
Please come back soon.
Thank you for watching.
I don't know why everyone thought I'd go on a break and not get it, but I did.
It's just so unexpected. I'm not wearing any gloves or anything.
I mean, I'm not even wearing gloves or anything, but I could probably skeletonize with just this.
Isn't that amazing?
What?
Look!
Wait, maybe not.
I'm not shaking it.
Thank you for watching!
Sendai Building
Halloween Apollo
Basin Manna
The one we usually use
I came here to hunt.
I was able to do it for about 3 months and a grade too!
I'm hungry, so I'm going back for more.
Listen, everyone.
I was pretty close to crying.
By the way, I really was.
I was about to cry a lot.
I worked really hard and it feels great.
I even thought about borrowing a lighter from a passerby.
I was about to cry a lot.
I couldn't do it.
I thought I'd just go home.
By the way, if I can't do this
I'll try one more time.
I'm, uh, I'm going to cry.
I've got to get there.
We made it.
We're here.
I hope I don't disappear.
I just hope it doesn't go away.
This is the only wood I bought today.
Well, I don't cook much, so it's okay.
Oh, thank God.
I was afraid it would end like this.
I've got to get it cleaned up.
It's clean.
Teslo's Road Town Building
ool
ucuc
I'm tired.
Today.
I'm making pasta.
I'm going to make pasta. Are you seeing this? I'll make pasta.
I'm making pasta. Meat pasta.
I've never made pasta before, but I'll do my best.
I'll make pasta.
Well, well, well. What do you think?
It looks so good!
Good afternoon.
I asked Pugh to come with me to Enoshima today to buy some KANAMI tampura.
Yay! I'm sorry.
I asked him to bring me.
Yeah...
Cucumbers look so good!
I'm so hungry because it's lunchtime right now!
So I'd like to go out to eat now!
I'm going!
Bye bye!
Ta-da!
Looks delicious!
Nama shiru soup and flounder!
Hirami looks delicious!
I tried the Hirame.
You put it on seafood.
Hey, the dressing!
Looks good, hika!
It looks so good!
I can't wait to try it.
I'm so hungry.
Let's eat soon.
Let's eat.
Hiyori said she'd bring it to me.
She said we could go in the morning.
She said we can go in the morning.
Let's eat
Bon appétit!
Let's take a picture.
Okay.
You want to drop your hand?
For now.
Here.
What's it look like?
What is this?
Which dressing is this?
I ate my seafood with it.
Right? First time.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good. It's absolutely delicious.
I've always wondered about that. It's delicious.
It's good.
Oh, my God, it's delicious.
What flavor?
What do you want?
Gomakko.
Gomikko.
I'm really not very good at this.
I can't crack it open.
It's like this every time.
I wonder if something bad is happening to me.
Something bad is happening to me.
Bon appétit!
Ta-da!
It's so beautifully cracked!
Oh, my God.
Are you sure?
Split foot.
Fluttering.
It's a good one.
It's good.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Yum! Yum!
Delicious.
Bon appétit.
Yum.
Delicious.
Fresh Chinese cabbage is delicious!
It's so soft and springy.
Delicious!
Soy sauce.
I put soy sauce on it.
I put wasabi.
Wow, that's a lot.
That's a lot of wasabi.
This glace is good, too.
Yum! Yum!
Bon appétit!
It's not good.
Delicious!
Mellow
Wasabi was spicy
It's normal.
Are you okay?
Bye-bye.
Thank you for dinner.Thank you for the food.
It was so delicious!
I ate the whole thing!
I ate it all up!
It was delicious!
The fresh Chinese cabbage was delicious!
The flounder was good, too.
It was delicious.
It's a tank of calamine.
I was so full.
I'm going to have some octopus.
Thanks for watching.
No problem.
Here's the octopus.
Looks delicious.
It smells so good.
Let's eat!
And Kanami's.
Oh, yeah, I got it!
This is the big one, just like it is!
I baked them at the store today.
Will it be rose-flavored calami?
I wonder if I can make it into a rose-flavored kalami
I wonder if I can make it into a rose-flavored caramid.
Bon appétit!
Eat it for me.
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Crispy.
Yummy.
Yeah, it's delicious.
Bon appétit.
This way.
Shirasu (baby sardine)
And ume plum and baby sardines.
Yes, ume-jako.
I like ume quite a lot.
I bought some ume-jako.
Look at that!
It's melted.
It's all wet.
We have to stop.
First, I'll just have a regular soft serve.
How's it taste?
Yeah. Shirasu.
Shirasu.
Oh, it fell out.
What?
It's got the texture of chilis.
It's just ice cream. It's delicious.
It's just...
Salty?
It's like a salt sauce.
It's good.
It's salty.
It's surprisingly good.
Yeah, it is.
Hey.
I'm going to Kamakura now!
You want to jump?
We're moving!
I'm not supposed to move this camera either.
Can't you?
Ready?
Ready!
Yeah!
Here we go!
Can you do it? That's me.
Woge.
We're in Kamakura.
We're here.
The chocolate terrine?
Yes, the terrine. I also bought a green tea terrine for Kanami.
It looks so delicious!
It's so good! I want some of that!
Kanami, give me a bite of this.
I really want a bite!
Looks so good!
But we're going to eat mochi shiratama now!
I recommend this place.
I hope they're open.
You're doing it.
Listen, everyone!
It was a low-class beauty.
It was a low-class place.
I was ready to eat.
I mean, it was a big risk-free thing, right?
Yes, yes, yes
Well, I'm sure there will be delicious food.
Kamakura.
I'm off!
I'll look for it.
I can find it.
Look at that!
Ta-da!
I got the green tea.
I'll go for the creamed almonds.
I don't want curry.
I don't want it.I don't want it.
Yes, I'm glad.
I'll eat it. You can imagine where I'm going to eat it.
Think about it.
I'm out of juice. Bye-bye.
I had a great time today. I had a great time.
We went to Aichi Island. I don't know. Not at all.
I came home with a really nice tumbler of calamari.
Yeah, I'm having so much fun.
I've been having a lot of fun with not taking it easy.
Okay, I'm gonna go for it. Let's go for it.
Bye-bye.